fantasygrounds.com 2016-06-07

# Fantasy Grounds :: The Virtual Tabletop for Pen & Paper Roleplaying Games

SmiteWorks USA, LLC is dedicated to respecting the privacy of the users of this web site as well as our customers and the users of our products. This privacy policy outlines the policies and practicies we follow in collecting, storing and using any personal information provided to us by the visitor or user or by the systems used to access our services, including web browsers.

**What types of information do we collect?**

We only collect personal information voluntarily submitted to us by visitors or users. This information may be submitted as a result of purchasing goods or services, completing a community registration procedure in order to access message boards or on-line services, or to take part in surveys, product registrations or newsletters. The information collected may include your name, e-mail address, home address or phone number, as well as a user name and password chosen by the user. We may also maintain a record of user specific preference settings for on-line services the user has registered for.

Visitors purchasing goods or services will also be required to submit information needed to complete the payment transactions. This information includes the credit card number, expiration date and billing address. Credit card data is not stored by SmiteWorks USA, LLC, but is required for the duration of the billing transaction.

We will record non-personal product activation data for purposes of controlling abuse and preventing unlawful use of the products for which this data has been created.

**How do we use the collected information?**

The personal information provided by the users is used to deliver the requested service for which the user submitted the information: fulfilling the order and delivering the product; delivering the service or operation; identifying the user or providing information as part of a customer service request; or delivering information about products, product updates or event, offer or promotion information requested by the user. Information collected for any purchases of licensed products is also shared with the Licensee of that product as part of our Royalty and Licensing agreement, as part of standard business practice and reporting.

The collected information can also be used in aggregate form to collect statistical information for internal marketing, profiling and demographic purposes. SmiteWorks may use data collected in aggregate for public, informational posts on gaming trends and to aid our business partners, who we have licensed products from.

**Who is collecting the information?**

All information is collected by SmiteWorks USA, LLC, unless specified otherwise. If/when a service is provided in co-operation with a third party, we try to make sure all parties observe good practices for privacy regarding personal information, and only share the information that is necessary for the delivery or realization of the service provided.

Please be aware that this privacy policy cannot control or apply to third parties linking to our site or services, or the content or operation of external content linked to from our site for purposes of providing information or services to our users.

**Use of cookies and internet protocol addresses**

We may use cookies and monitor internet protocol (IP) addresses of visitors for technical purposes, and for the purposes of providing better web services to our users. Such use may include automatic login or user preference tracking for on-line services. We may track IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, aggregate statistic reports, site traffic monitoring and server or service abuse control.

**How do we secure personal information?**

Access to all personal information is strictly controlled using industry standard authentication methods. Any sensitive information such as credit card information is transferred using SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption.

**What do I do if I have a question or complaint?**

If at any time you have questions about the personal information collected or wish to correct or request that we delete such information, please contact us (by e-mail) at contact@smiteworks.com or (by postal mail) at SmiteWorks USA, LLC, 7703 Hall Farm Drive, Louisville, KY 40291

By using this website or the Fantasy Grounds client software, you signify your assent to this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use this site. This document may be updated, please return to this address periodically to make sure that you are aware of any changes.

This privacy policy was last updated on January 16, 2015.
